game a is a complex game of tug-of-war
with multiple multiple ropes people come
in to game be looking for which rope
they can pull behind which one is going
to have the biggest chance about
competing game a of destroying everybody
else except all the NGOs all the other
projects all have their own rope and
they're all pulling in opposite
directions what they want to do is get
everyone pulling in the same direction
not gonna happen to play game B we first
have to drop the rope so all the people
that look like they're standing around
doing nothing doing the personal work
they've dropped the rope and they're
looking for and to rival rasam neuen
solutions other games to play that will
entice people over from the game of rope
now it looks like someone's like well
yeah let's just play soccer that's way
better that's picking up a rope pulling
them in the in the direction of soccer
you have to just start playing soccer
and then they will see in the corner and
play pulling the rope your direction is
not game B you first have to drop the
rope